<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JudaicaLink</title>
    <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on JudaicaLink</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 10:38:06 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>YIVO_ENCYCLOPEDIA</title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/encyclopedia/YIVO_ENCYCLOPEDIA/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 10:38:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/encyclopedia/YIVO_ENCYCLOPEDIA/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;yivo-encyclopedia:f131778e49efad5f85f27bd726633c49&#34;&gt;YIVO ENCYCLOPEDIA&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/img/yivo_logo_black-on-white-135x68.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The YIVO Encyclopedia of Jews in Eastern Europe, courtesy of the YIVO Institute of Jewish Research, NY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only resource of its kind, this encyclopedia provides the most complete picture of the history and culture of Jews in Eastern Europe from the beginnings of their settlement in the region to the present. This website makes accurate, reliable, scholarly information about East European Jewish life accessible to everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The YIVO Encyclopedia is so compulsively browsable that you can disappear within its pages for hours without a trace, the equivalent of diving into the coolest, deepest of pools.” —Kenneth Turan, L.A. Times&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>invited_Talk_Rome</title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/news/invited_Talk_Rome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2016 12:52:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/news/invited_Talk_Rome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last week, Kai Eckert was invited to present JudaicaLink in Rome at the Workshop Linked Open Data &amp;amp; Jewish Cultural Heritage. Here are the slides:&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/about_us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/about_us/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;initiators:e23bae1993678f66ca1fc108ea63c12b&#34;&gt;Initiators:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;kai-eckert:e23bae1993678f66ca1fc108ea63c12b&#34;&gt;Kai Eckert&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/img/kai-portrait-600px.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;
Kai Eckert is a research associate at the Chair of Chris Bizer, University of Mannheim, where he leads the infrastructure development of the EU funded project DM2E (Digitised Manuscripts to Europeana). Kai Eckert is a computer and information scientist with a PhD from the University of Mannheim and master degrees from the University of Mannheim (Computer Science, Business Informatics) and the Humboldt-University of Berlin (MA LIS). He is an internationally known expert for Linked Data in libraries and cultural heritage institutions. His goal is the access to digital cultural assets and the scholarly knowledge via the web of data in order to create new applications that drive the research in the digital humanities. For contact, see here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;dov-winer:e23bae1993678f66ca1fc108ea63c12b&#34;&gt;Dov Winer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/img/dov_winer.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;
Dov Winer is a psychologist (Hebrew University) who specialized in Online Education and Training (University of London). He was involved in the early introduction of the Internet in Israel having established the Israel Internet Society and promoted a W3C office there. He coordinates the Israel MINERVA forum for technology applications in culture whose membership includes the relevant cultural heritage institutions of the country; he co-chairs the annual Jerusalem EVA/Minerva International Conference for the Digitisation of Culture. As an in-house consultant of the European Association of Jewish Culture (UK) he is the Scientific Manager of Judaica Europeana.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/legal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/legal/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;impressum:7d11b95da6f13f352e32f5af2c24f251&#34;&gt;Impressum&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Verantwortlich für den Inhalt dieser Website:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WISS Research Group 2016&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prof. Dr. Kai Eckert&lt;br /&gt;
Hochschule der Medien&lt;br /&gt;
Nobelstr. 10&lt;br /&gt;
D-70569 Stuttgart&lt;br /&gt;
Germany&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Phone:&lt;/strong&gt; +49 (0) 711 8923-3164&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Es gilt das &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hdm-stuttgart.de/impressum&#34;&gt;Impressum der Hochschule der Medien&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Die Hochschule der Medien Stuttgart ist eine Körperschaft des öffentlichen Rechts. Sie wird durch den Rektor Professor Dr. Alexander W. Roos gesetzlich vertreten.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;USt.-ID-Nr.:&lt;/strong&gt; DE 224 427 890&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zuständige Aufsichtsbehörde:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ministerium für Wissenschaft, Forschung und Kunst Baden-Württemberg&lt;br /&gt;
Königstraße 46&lt;br /&gt;
70173 Stuttgart&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/vision/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;vision:5d5d65284fe4370ad9e27d777ba2c3e1&#34;&gt;VISION&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;linking-reference-works-of-the-jewish-culture-and-history:5d5d65284fe4370ad9e27d777ba2c3e1&#34;&gt;LINKING REFERENCE WORKS OF THE JEWISH CULTURE AND HISTORY&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scholarly reference works like encyclopediae, glossars, or catalogs function as guides to a scholarly domain and as anchor points and manifestations of scholarly work. On the web of Linked Data, they can take on a key function to interlink resources related to the described concepts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JudaicaLink provides support to publish and interlink existing reference works of the Jewish culture and history as Linked Data. We are currently in the planning phase with several maintainers and publishers of such reference works. Stay tuned for further information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in joining us, either because you are responsible for a reference work or because you want to support us, please contact &lt;a href=&#34;http://wiss.iuk.hdm-stuttgart.de/people/kai-eckert/&#34;&gt; Kai Eckert &lt;/a&gt; .&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>